<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Tanmay Dutta</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Tanmay Dutta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love spell</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/love_spell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1/services/love_spell/</guid>
      <description>Yes, love spells are real. You don’t ask for much out of life as you have simple needs. But you must have that special person in your life who appreciates your warmth, your inner beauty, your essence. After casting this spell the person may grow strong feelings for you and finally ask to be with you.
Types of Love spells Attraction Spell This is a basic attraction spell for finding someone new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psychic Reading</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/psychic_reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1/services/psychic_reading/</guid>
      <description>A psychic reading is a specific attempt to discern information through the use of heightened perceptive abilities; or natural extensions of the basic human senses of sight, sound, touch, taste and instinct. Tanmay Dutta can tap into the past, present, and future to gain valuable insight into a situation that is troubling you. Most of the time, i use clairvoyance to see into the future and provide details about what will happen and when.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual Healing</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/spiritual_healing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1/services/spiritual_healing/</guid>
      <description>Tanmay Dutta can gives best results for all spiritual healing problems he can perform otherworldly vitality healing. Spiritual healing works on all facets of the person – past, present and future – restoring and opening the natural lines for personal success in mind, body and spirit.
I believe that all illness comes from losing power or giving power away to something or someone. It may be spirits from the Inner World that you have traded your soul power with to get fame or fortune or love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Spells</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/money_spells/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1/services/money_spells/</guid>
      <description>Money spells to help you get or win a large sum of money so that you have all the money you have always dreamed to have. Money spell will help you with money problems towards a life filled with money and financial success.
If you are not doing well financially get a money spell that will enhance your money making abilities and money attraction capabilities. You will start experiencing coincidences that result in you coming into contract with various opportunities to make money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palm reading</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1/services/palm_reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1/services/palm_reading/</guid>
      <description>We all are well known with the term &amp;ldquo;Mind, Body and Soul&amp;rdquo;, but we have never been taught the importance of your palm and fingers, when it comes to the spiritual connection and enlightenment. As a norm, we still hold our thumb with the Saturn (long) finger but most of us don&amp;rsquo;t know what does it means!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
